- It's as you say.
When you start here you are like this, will I get some friends?
Because you come here yourself for the most part.
But I got friends too.
Not to brag.
- Lovely!
- To start with, you have the introduction immediately when you start.
Which is a great way to get to know people.
Both in their own class, but also on other programs.
Several of those who are my closest friends today, I met the first few days when I came here.
So it's really fun!
- Learn all the houses and where all the halls are located.
- It was something you felt in the beginning when you walked around and found nowhere.
- No.
- Neither in the city nor here on campus.
- There is a lot you can get involved in.
I go to the medical program and then we have something called the Medical Association.
Which in turn has many different committees.
In one of them I have been and still engaged.
It is really great fun and promotes student life and the relationship of the program itself.
- I chose to get involved in the Legal Association and it has been great fun.
Then you control bales, sessions and trips abroad.
- Go to Åre!
And go on a ball in other cities, so it has been super fun.
- You choose how committed you want to be.
I have probably been the one who has been more involved at least at first.
When you just get into student life and are a new student.
Then I have also been involved in committees.
I have been a member of the study social committee.
We have arranged lots of different activities for all students in the section.
Among other things, arranged sessions.
- I've done a lot actually.
Engaged me within my section.
I study at the School of Economics, then I belong to Sesame.
- Correct!
- It is wonderful!
Then I have been involved in everything possible.
Among other things, have been sitting on the board, very fun.
There are lots of different assignments and committees with different orientations that you can find.
There is really everything possible to do.
- It's great when creating activities,
Because then you meet people from different programs or grades.
- Then you can arrange things together between other courses as well.
- Then I have also been involved outside my section, in Örebro Kårhus.
- Fun!
- Which is for students, by students.
There I have been an ambassador and helped get people in so they come,
And that people work ideally, which is very fun and a good experience.
At Örebro Kårhus you can sit in the cafe in the days and plug in and meet people.
- Really!
- Late in the evenings, on Thursdays there is a Thursday pub.
- The music quiz!
Above all.
- Music quiz, very fun.
On Fridays we saddle and put on the dance shoes.
- Lol!
- So we go out and party a little.
It is very fun to party with its fellow students.
- Even if you feel uncertainty when you come here.
Dare to participate in the introduction is something I actually think everyone should bring,
And do when you come.